A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
Joma, Joma Dabarasa.
As Grand Witch I now declare this witch's mass open, let us begin.
Crona, Ragnarok, come along.
Yes, ma'am, Lady Medusa.
Yes, ma'am.
Anyway, this is your power!
Connect with the...
We must numb our heart
Thank you.
Hold on a moment.
Oh, dear.
What's happening? She won't let us go.
I don't think I know how to deal with this situation.
You can deal with it by shutting up and giving me all your money.
Good evening, Erica Frog.
Did you need something?
Ribbit.
I think you know why I'm stopping you.
Oh, yes.
But come on, it's not as if I'm the only one who brought non-witches to the gathering tonight.
Over there, that little witch is accompanied by a human, so you see it's not just me.
The purity of the witch's mass certainly has gone downhill.
But that isn't what I wanted to talk to you about tonight, Medusa.
I have some questions for you.
First, what were you doing stealing something from the Grand Witch's room?
And second, you snuck yourself onto the staff at the DWMA.
Why in the world would you do that?
Krona, give me my coat.
Yes, right away, Lady Medusa.
My research at the Academy has been fully approved, as you well know.
The Grand Witch herself is on my side, Erika.
Just a minute.
The Grand Witch's eyesight is failing.
She doesn't see what a nuisance you've made of yourself lately.
That Academy is there to hunt down witches.
You know that as well as I do.
If you slip up just once, you won't be the only one in trouble.
You'll take us down with you.
And then there's him.
Why would you try to create a Kishin that could potentially be an enemy to our kind?
You've taken it too far.
It's time for you to starve.
You meddlesome little frog and mouse.
I think I'm going to have to punish you.
Perhaps not right now, though.
I'm in a hurry.
With so many students to look after, the school nurse mustn't be late.
Joma joma davarasa.
I can't stand that witch, stupid snake woman.
Courage that beats out fear.
Maka Albarn's great resolution?
Turn around for me.
And tell me how you've been feeling.
More or less normal, I guess.
Except for lately, I've been having this really weird dream over and over again.
A strange dream, you say?
Yeah.
And it's been bothering me because I can remember it so clearly.
I always start out in this room that's pitch black.
There's a record player, and it's always skipping like the record's scratched or something.
The music that's playing is some kind of jazz song that I think I've heard before but can't really place.
After I've been sitting there for a bit, this guy always appears from the other side of the room.
He's a little demon wearing a fancy suit and dancing this weird dance out of time with the music.
Swing, swing, swing.
Dude, this is jazz. It isn't swing music.
But jazz is so much more appropriate for nighttime.
Far as I know, music's not picky about when it gets played.
You can decide, so why not listen to swing?
That's right. The decision's mine. Yes, sir.
You can decide, too. You're eligible.
When you were cut open like a fish being gutted, you must have been afraid, am I right?
And wouldn't it be nice to have a strong mind, one that can get rid of the fear you feel?
If you forget your fear, you'll become reckless.
That's something they teach at the Academy.
Heh. What kind of fool are you?
Do you think you're in heaven where you can't get hurt again?
Hate to break it to you, but you're still on Earth.
And if you want to stay alive down here, you're going to need more power than you've got now.
Power so overwhelmingly strong, you can say goodbye to all your fears.
You're nothing without that power.
Now come on and get out there already.
Now wait, hold on a second.
Please, I don't want to leave this room.
Let me stay here until the dream is over and I wake up.
I'll even put up with the lame music.
Seek out the power you need.
Find a rule to break.
It will make you stronger.
Stronger, perhaps, than you thought possible.
What makes you so afraid of leaving the room, Sol?
When I leave the room, the darkness continues.
Then all of a sudden I see this light and I move toward it.
But when I go through...
When I go through, I'm coming out of Maka's stomach.
Interesting.
The black blood that's entered his body seems to be having an effect on him.
So, aside from all that, how am I doing?
Well, you still have a slight arrhythmia,
but you seem to be making a nice recovery so far.
Let's just take your blood pressure.
As for this strange dream of yours,
it's not unusual to have recurring nightmares
after going through the trauma that you have.
I don't think you need to be worried.
Is that all?
Or was there something else you've been concerned about?
Well, I don't know if concerned is the right word for it exactly.
But ever since we got back from Italy,
Maka's been acting all strange.
I think something's been bothering her.
Really?
I'm sorry to hear that.
A jar?
That's right, a jar.
Is it a special jar?
Nope, nothing special.
It's just an ordinary jar.
Now, the water that's inside the jar is another story altogether.
It's called soul-sapping water
because it sucks out your soul wavelength.
Compared to that, the jar's very ordinary indeed.
Go on, try sticking your hand in the water.
All right, but I'm still a little iffy about this jar.
What was that?
I knew that jar was dangerous.
No, it's just the water.
You might want to start off by sticking in only one finger at a time.
All I have to do is get to where I can withstand putting my whole hand in there,
and then I can use Tsubaki's enchanted sword mode, professor?
That's the basic idea.
That'll be a nice break.
All I've been doing lately is muscle conditioning, and it's getting old.
Huh?
What's with you?
It isn't fair.
How can you get stronger just by playing with a jar filled with water?
Ha!
Isn't it obvious?
I'm Blackstar.
I'm on a whole different level than you.
I'm a big man.
I've beaten death.
Who else can say that?
No fair.
Professor Stein, can I have one of those special jars, too?
I can't do that.
The water in the jar is only intended to help Blackstar be able to use Tsubaki's enchanted
sword mode.
I'm not going to let myself get beaten by a jar.
I don't care how special it is.
I'd be surprised if Blackstar even realized what he was doing by saying things like that.
By talking constantly about what a star he is and how big he is, Blackstar is actually
driving himself without even meaning to.
Driving himself?
Yes.
There's no stage too big for me.
Of course I can do it.
But that's his answer to any challenge he faces.
And once he's said that, he will put every effort into making it happen, because he's
already decided he will succeed.
Blackstar is trying to surpass death.
He is bound to become stronger.
Right.
But that's his way of making himself stronger.
It's not a method that will work for everybody.
You have to find your own way to do it, something that works for you.
My own way of becoming stronger?
Right now you're definitely lacking something, Maka.
A certain level of stress and anxiety is understandable, but you don't want to take it too far.
Wait, what do you mean lacking something?
Once you figure out what it is, come see me and we'll decide what to do about it.
Didn't I tell you to start out with only one finger?
You can take the jar with you.
The lesson's over for now.
Hey, Maka, what about the party?
Oh, yeah, I almost forgot.
I was going to throw a party to congratulate Tsubaki and Blackstar since they finally managed
to collect a soul and to celebrate the fact that Soul's coming home.
Be sure to have some good fish dishes, okay?
He's strong, huh?
Okay, soul.
I expect to see you back here in one week.
Excuse me.
Hey.
I'm going home to get ready for the party.
See you there.
Something does seem to be bothering her.
Is it the scar?
Yeah, that happens every time she sees it.
She gets this pained look.
Well, it may not have been tasty, but it sure was filling.
Hey, I've got an idea.
Next time you do the cooking.
Don't listen to him, Maka.
It was delicious.
Yum, yum.
Yeah, thank you for the snacks.
You guys have a nice place here.
It's so tidy.
You must make a point of keeping it clean.
It helps that Maka yells at me whenever I make a mess.
Is it just the two of you living here, then?
Yoo-hoo!
Is everyone having a good time?
Which one of you little boys wants to come and take a bath with me?
The water's nice and warm.
Is it always like this over here?
Oh, yeah.
Anybody want to take the sexy kitty home, she's free.
Infiltrating the academy was worth the risk.
I'll need to run some tests on Sol now that he has Ragnarok's black blood inside him.
With this key, it should be easy.
Well, what a coincidence running into you here.
Have you already guessed what we're doing here, Medusa?
Or should I tell you?
Oh, please.
Tell me.
Ribbit, ribbit.
All right, then I will.
We've come here to kill you.
Oh, no, but that's terrible.
I thought we were friends.
Don't take it personally.
We simply have no interest in attracting the attention of the Grim Reaper.
And we don't care for whatever little experiments you're doing at the academy, either.
You're now a liability, Medusa.
And liabilities must be killed.
Before you do that, though, may I offer you a little piece of advice?
That outfit is a liability, too.
It simply screams witch.
Whether you're casting soul protect or not, there are a good number of young maesters wandering these streets who know a witch when they see one.
Sweet of you to warn us, but don't you worry.
If it comes to it, we can use our transformation magic to escape, which is a luxury you don't have.
I see now.
So that's how you're planning to beat me, is it?
We know we couldn't beat you in a fight under ordinary circumstances.
But here in Death City, you need to maintain your cover as a school nurse.
You can't drop your soul protect and use magic to defend yourself.
That would be a dead giveaway.
You're cornered.
All we have to do is attack you while you're using soul protect.
If you don't fight back, we'll defeat you easily.
And if you do release your soul protect to attack us, we'll transform and make a clean escape.
Meanwhile, you'll be revealed to the maesters as a witch, and they'll hunt you down.
Whatever you decide to do, we still win.
Not a bad plan, wouldn't you say?
And that's how the frog and mouse will beat the snake.
Tonight, you'll be the one croaking, not me.
Funny how the world works.
If you're going to kill me, please don't make me listen to your bad jokes first.
That's just plain cruel.
Soul protect, release!
You're finished.
Say goodbye now.
That soul wavelength.
Witch!
What's up, Maka?
You startled us.
It's two witches.
What are they doing in Death City?
Sorry, guys.
I'll be right back.
Hey, Maka, what gives?
I would love nothing more than to hear your screams as you're writhing in agony.
But I'm afraid we don't have time for that.
How unfortunate.
You do have the brains of a frog and a mouse.
Only stupid creatures would try to defeat me this way.
You will be punished.
Too bad you aren't even fit to serve as research subjects.
If you're going to fight, all we have to do is run.
What is she waiting for?
Why isn't she releasing her soul protect?
Wait a second.
Where are the tattoos that were on your shoulder?
Oh, my.
They seem to have disappeared, haven't they?
Mizune, what's wrong?
The snakes!
You put them inside of Mizune's body!
There's no way.
When could you have...
You did it last night!
I have thousands of snakes stored in my body, waiting to do whatever I say.
Those are only a few of them.
Please, Jene.
My snakes will consume her until there's nothing left.
But how could you?
The snakes are magic too, aren't they?
And you haven't released your soul protect.
So how are you?
These little ones have magic of their own.
I don't have to release my soul protect to use them.
This one's my pride and joy.
She's such an obedient and effective little darling.
An impressive trick, wouldn't you say?
You must realize by now,
Mizune isn't the only one my darlings have slithered inside.
That didn't take long.
Stein and Maka.
Are you all right, Dr. Medusa?
We detected two witches in this area and came as quickly as we could.
Yes.
I sensed them too and came here to investigate them myself.
I wonder if one of them could have been the witch who was there when Sol was injured.
That is a possibility.
No, I don't think it's the same one.
For one thing, that witch had the demon sword and its meister along with her.
And even if she had been here, I doubt we would have sensed her at all.
I have a feeling that this one is too cunning to release her protect in the middle of Death City without reason.
One thing we do know is that this witch has an interest in weapons and meisters.
So I wouldn't be surprised if she was in the area observing the students here.
But I have no doubt she would want to do it quietly.
Yes.
I suppose it's even possible that she has managed to infiltrate the academy itself.
But that would be tricky even for a powerful witch.
Whatever the case, it's a relief that you weren't hurt by these witches, Dr. Medusa.
We would be in some serious trouble if anything happened to our only school nurse.
Thanks, but I'm fine.
But still, if I ever see that sword and its meister again...
I don't know how much longer I can handle this.
I know I promised myself I'd become stronger, but...
Maka!
Are you all right, Maka?
You shouldn't take off on your own.
It's too dangerous.
I'm fine, Sol.
Hmm?
Shh!
I couldn't do it.
I couldn't bring myself to look at Sol's scar.
I have to find a way to face this scar
I can't let Sol get hurt like that again
I refuse to let my fear control me anymore
You have to tell me what's going on
All right, Professor Stein
Yes?
I know what I'm lacking now
You told me to figure it out and I have
Very good
At last, Makas finally found the courage to fight her fear
In that case, I'd like you and Sol to come to my office tomorrow for a special lesson
I've come far enough
I should be able to rest a bit now
Next time I really am going to kill you, Medusa Ribbit
Ah, yes
That feels nice and cool on my foot
I could get used to this
That's her, isn't it?
I thought I was safe
There's just one tiny favor I need to ask of you, Erika
A key?
I don't understand
How does he know where he was?
The snakes inside you told me
It doesn't matter how far you run
From now on, I'll know wherever you go
Now about that favor
There's a man I'd like you to release using that key
His witch prison number is 13
Unless you're a very stupid frog
I'm sure you know who I'm talking about
You don't mean the man with the magic eye
But he's the one who took the grand witch's left eye
If I free him, I'll be banished from the witch world forever
No, they'll probably just kill me
I can kill you right here if you'd prefer
Ribbit, fine, I'll do it
There's a little experiment I'm going to do
Using the man with the magic eye
Some questions I have concerning Soli
You're going to use him for an experiment?
What are you thinking?
You're out of your mind, Ribbit
You don't feel as good on my foot now
Change yourself back into a frog
Okay
Plus two, plus one, plus two, plus one, plus two, plus one, plus two, plus one, plus two, plus one
He's at it again
That's getting so annoying
What is the answer?
How many times did I multiply?
One, plus two, plus one, plus two, plus one
Tell me the answer
How many times did I multiply?
You're just in there adding ones and twos
You haven't multiplied anything yet
I can't see
I can't see anything
It's been ages since I've seen a good comedy
I want to be
Look that you can exceed the phosphat meglio
I wanna be
Let's go
I wanna
I wanna be my son of a
絶望と一緒に
悲鳴をあげ
突き刺され
全てが変わる前に
I wanna be my son of a
On the next episode of soul eater the man with the magic eye soul and makas diverging soul wavelength
Make snake Cobra Cobra get out of this preview. It's mine. No
impossible